It is the turbulent Sengoku period.
어지러운 전국 시대.
Warlords keep on fighting day and night over Jipangu State, where Karakuri people live.
카라쿠리인이 사는 지팡구국에서는 군웅할거하여 밤낮으로 접전이 계속되고
Karakuri martial artists were sharpening their swords, dreaming of victory and honor.
카라쿠리 무예가들도 승리와 영광을 꿈꾸며 맹렬히 싸우고 있었다.
And now, a wild hero has arrived, seeking to be the number one Karakuri martial artist!
그리고 지금, 카라쿠리 무예가 제일을 꿈꾸는 터무니없는 영웅이 탄생했다!
Musashi is here-dasu!
무사시 등장이오!
Karakuri Kengouden
카라쿠리 검호전: 무사시 로드
A man always dreams of the day
사내는 언제나 세계 한가운데서
in the center of the world to become
제일 강해질 날을
AH! AH! the strongest
아! 아! 꿈꿔라
Raise the sword of your heart high to the wide sky
마음의 칼을 넓은 하늘로 번쩍 쳐들어
Raise the curtain to the road of adventure
모험의 길의 막을 연다
A skilled swordsman roams on Jipangu State
지팡구국을 떠도는 검호
His name is Musashi, a Karakuri man
그 이름은 카라쿠리인 무사시
Go! Fight!
가라! 싸워라!
The sound of fierce duels
격렬한 승부의 소리는
makes life dazzling
눈부신 인생
Battles of yesterdays make you stronger today
싸웠던 어제보다도 오늘 강해진다
Martial Arts! Dual Blade Musashi
무예! 이도류 무사시
Tomorrow will be glorious
내일은 빛난다
The sound of fierce duels
격렬한 승부의 소리는
makes life dazzling
눈부신 인생
Fight the utmost with the stillness
싸우는 한껏 고요함과 함께
Martial Arts! Dual Blade Musashi
무예! 이도류 무사시
His eyes shined! Musashi!
미간이 반짝였다 무사시!!
Musashi and Kojirō was assigned guard duty during the journey of finding Senhime's husband.
센히메의 신랑을 찾는 여행에서 방호 역을 맡은 무사시와 코지로.
Out of nowhere, Jiraiyan, one of the Four Rulers, attacked Senhime per instructions from Hanzō.
그 센히메를 느닷없이 덮친 건 한조에게 지령을 받은 사천왕 중 하나, 지라이얀.
Musashi and Kojirō were in peril. But Senhime played her flute to their rescue.
위태로웠던 무사시와 코지로. 그 때, 둘 위기를 구해준 건 센히메의 피리였다.
Beautiful Woman
미녀 오니히메 나타나오
So good! Granma, one more dish of dumplings-dasu!
맛있소! 할머니, 만두 하나 더 주시오.
-That's enough! -What?
-이제 그만! -뭐시라?
You already had five dishes!
5접시 먹었으면 충분하다!
What about you?!
코지로는!
I only had two dishes.
난 두 접시다.
I had only two, too.
나도 두 접시야.
Musashi! You are my assistant! My assistant eating more than me is unforgivable!
무사시, 넌 내 조수다! 조수가 나보다 많이 먹는다니 용서할 수 없다!
How much was it?
얼마 나왔나?
It's 10 mons.
예, 10문입니다.
Man, he's getting all snobby for having the wallet...
진짜, 자기만 돈을 가지고 있으니 잘난 척은...
Don't you agree, Osenchan?
그치, 오센짱?
Hey, a good man!
오, 좋은 남자!
I'm Osen. How should I call you?
나, 오센이라고 해. 넌?
I am Hikarinosuke Genji.
나는 겐지 히카리노스케.
Hikarinosuke Genji! What a good name!
겐지 히카리노스케! 멋진 이름!
Would you like to have some manjus with me?
저기저기, 같이 만쥬 안 먹을래?
Manju?
만쥬?
What's so funny?
뭐가 이상해?
Sorry. I'm happy that you asked me, but those are for girls and old people.
미안미안. 바로 제안받아서 기쁘긴 해도 저건 아녀자나 늙은이가 먹는 것.
-Hey, what's that? -Never heard of Shamisen?
-저기, 그거 뭐야? -삼현금 몰라?
I know, but I never saw it on back.
알긴 해도 등에 매다니.
Awesome!
멋져!
Do you really think so?
정말 그렇게 생각해?
I don't lie. I can play this a little bit.
거짓말은 안해. 나도 이걸 좀 할 줄 알아.
Cool, I was traveling to look for fresh musics.
오, 나, 새로운 음악을 위해 여행하고 있어.
I'm traveling too!
나도 여행하고 있어!
Then shall we go together?
그럼 같이 갈까?
I think musics represent the heart.
나, 음악이라는 것은 마음이라고 생각해.
Hey, Osenchan!
어, 오센짱!
Did you forget why are we on this trip?
이 여행의 목적을 잊었나!
It is to find a husband for Senhime. Remember? We only have to protect her from danger.
센히메의 신랑을 찾는 것이다. 알겠냐? 우리는 단지 센히메를 위험에서 보호해 드리기만 하면 된다.
Meanwhile at Edotopia, Hanzō was...
그 때, 에도토피아의 한조는...
General Ieyasu, I'll show you soon.
제너럴 이에야스, 지금 보여주겠다.
I, Hanzō, the shadow shōgun, will take over the world.
천하는 이 어둠의 쇼군, 한조가 가져가겠다.
For that, Ieyasu's granddaughter, Senhime, must be dealt with first.
그를 위해 이에야스의 손녀 센히메를...
Tell Onihime to take Musashi and Kojirō down!
오니히메에게 전달해라. 무사시, 코지로를 쓰러뜨리라고!
What's so good about that guy-dasu?! I totally can't understand Osenchan-dasu. Don't you agree, Kojirō?
저런 남자의 뭐가 좋소! 정말 오센짱은 알다가도 모르겠소! 안 그렇소, 코지로?
Didn't you hear me asking-dasu?!
안 그렇소라고 말하는 게 안 들리오?!
Whoever she likes, I have nothing to do with that.
사람이 누굴 좋아하든 나하고는 관계없는 일이다.
That might be true, but I still don't like him-dasu.
그건 그럴지 모르겠어도 역시 마음에 안 드오.
Hey!
아!
What's is it, Musashi?
왜 그러냐, 무사시?
Follow me-dasu!
큰일이오!
H- hey! What's wrong-dasu? Wake up-dasu!
어, 어이! 무슨 일이오! 정신 차리시오!
Help me! I'm scared!
도와줘, 무서워!
A monster showed up in our village...
마, 마을에 괴물이 나와서...
Elaborate!
자세히 설명해 봐라!
A monster named Tsuchigumo has appeared in our Miyazato village...
미야자토 마을이라고 하는 곳에 츠치구모라는 괴물이 나타나서...
What? Tsuchigumo?
뭐라? 츠치구모가?
That Tsuchigumo is taking...
그 츠치구모가 마을 사람들을...
taking villagers...
마을 사람들을 덮쳐서...
Yamata no Orochi?
야마타노오로치?
Tsuchigumo?
츠치구모?
They are monsters that are told to be protecting the sacred swords named Tenkūmaru and Tenchimaru.
신이 다스리던 시대부터 명도 천공환, 천지환을 지키고 있다고 전해지는 괴물입니다.
So by getting rid of those monsters, I will claim those excellent swords-dasu!
그 괴물을 퇴치하면 그 명도가 손에 들어오는 것이오!
When that time comes, Musashi, you'll become the best of the best swordsmen around the world.
그 때야말로 무사시 님은 천하제일의 검호가 되겠죠.
Thank you so much-dasu, Jūbee!
주베 씨, 감사하오!
I'll do that with all my might!
나, 힘껏 해 보겠소!
Tenkūmaru from Yamata no Orochi. Tenchimaru from Tsuchigumo.
야마타노오로치가 천공환. 츠치구모가 천지환.
I'll be able to get that Tenchimaru-dasu.
그 천지환을 손에 넣을 수 있소.
Here I go!
이럇!
Musashi, where are you going?
무사시, 어디 가?
I'm going to get Tsuchigumo!
츠치구모를 잡으러 가오!
This way is to Miyazato village!
미야자토 마을은 이쪽이에요!
I am interested in monsters.
나, 괴물에 흥미가 있어.
Hikarinosuke, wait for me!
히카리노스케 씨, 기다려!
I will take down Tsuchigumo-dasu!
츠치구모는 내가 쓰러뜨리오!
By taking Tsuchigumo down, Tenchimaru will become his. But what kind of monster is waiting for him?
츠치구모를 쓰러뜨리면 천지환을 손에 넣을 수 있다. 그러나 가는 길에 기다리고 있는 것은 어떤 괴물일 것인가?
Are you alright?
괜찮아?
Speaking of which, we've been walking nonstop. Let's take a short break.
그러고 보니 아까부터 계속 걸어만 왔다. 조금 쉬자.
The village is up ahead. I'll let the villagers know that strong samurais are here to take down Tsuchigumo!
마을은 곧 나와요. 저, 모두한테 강한 사무라이님들이 츠치구모를 쓰러뜨리러 왔다고 사람들에게 전달하러 갈게요!
Don't forget to tell tham that they can depend on Musashi in particular-dasu!
특히 무사시한테 의지해도 된다고 잘 말해주시오!
Yes!
네!
Musashi knows no shame.
입은 살았네, 무사시도 참.
One thing Musashi's good at would be being cheeky.
넉살 좋은 게 무사시의 좋은 점이니까요.
Figures.
역시 그런가.
What was that-dasu?!
뭣이오?!
There's no village here.
마을이 아예 없잖아.
Where did that Otama go?
그 오타마라는 여자아이, 어디에 가 버렸는가...
Hey! Otama! Where did you go-dasu?!
어이! 오타마! 어디에 갔소!
Come out! Otama!
나오시오! 오타마!
Could it be that she was up to something?!
설마 뭔가 노리던 건가!
Up to something?
노려?
That girl might have been planning to deceive us at the first place.
그 여자아이, 처음부터 우리를 속일 생각이었던 것일지도.
For what?
뭐하러?
She could have misled us, so that once we get tired, Tsuchigumo can strike us.
우리를 길을 잃게 하고, 지쳤을 때 츠치구모가 덤벼들면...
W- what the-dasu... It was just a bat...
뭐, 뭐오. 단지 박쥐이오.
And you get surprised by that?!
그런 거에 깜짝 놀라긴!
I just thought I might see something by climbing up the tree-dasu!
나무에 오르면 뭔가 보이지 않을까 하고 생각했소!
No way Otama would have deceived us-dasu!
오타마가 속이다니, 생각할 수도 없소!
And you. Kojirō, right?
너 코지로라 했지?
I think you have too much suspicions!
너도 좀 의심이 많은 것 같은데!
Is enemies incoming the only thing you ever think about?
언제 적이 올까밖에 생각하고 있지 않으면 어쩌자는 거야.
I was...
난...
I can see a light-dasu!
아, 빛이 보이오!
I see a light there-dasu!
저기에 빛이 있소!
There is a house-dasu!
집이 있소!
There really is a house!
정말 집이다!
Yay! I can now have a meal-dasu!
잘됐소! 이제 밥을 먹을 수 있소!
Anyone?
누구 있소?
Yes, I'll be there soon.
네, 네, 곧 나옵니다.
Who are you?
누구십니까?
Are we at Miyazato village-dasu?
여긴 미야자토 마을이오?
Only two more mountains to pass.
미야자토 마을은 단지 산 두개만 넘으면 나와요.
T- two mountains?!
사, 산을 둘씩이나?!
As there was an avalanche on the road, you probably wouldn't want to continue on now.
가는 길이 산사태로 막혀 있으니까 지금 가는 건 무리에요.
But a girl named Otama from that village...
그래도 오타마라는 마을의 여자얘가...
Oh, Otama ran to the village some time ago.
아, 오타마라면 아까 마을에 달려서 돌아갔소.
Huh?
어?
Miyazato village does exist. No way that kid would have deceived us.
미야자토 마을도 분명 있네. 그 아이는 역시 우리를 속인 게 아니야.
But... how could Otama make it through the blocked road from an avalanche?
그래도... 산사태가 났다는데 오타마는 어떻게 오갈 수 있던 거야?
That's because she lives there and thus she can easily climb up and down the rock mountain.
그건 자기가 사는 곳이니까 빠르게 바위산을 넘나들 수 있는 거지. 낮이라면 너희들도 갈 수 있어요.
Then do we have to wait until tomorrow morning-dasu?
그럼 내일 아침까지 기다려야 하오...
There's nothing much here, but you can stay here if you want to.
이런 누추한 곳이라도 괜찮다면 잠시 쉬어가쇼.
Thank you so much! We must do so-
우와, 고맙소! 그렇게 해야겠-
And we'd like a meal too...
그 김에 밥도...
Yay!
야호!
There's not much than rice, so please, suit yourself.
반찬 없는 단순한 밥일 뿐이니 밥이라도 가득 드쇼.
Really, there's nothing at all, but it tastes so good-dasu!
정말, 반찬이 아무것도 없는데도 맛있소.
Musashi!
무사시!
That is a rude thing to say!
그렇게 말하는 건 실례야!
Is praising for the good taste bad-dasu?
맛있다고 칭찬하는 게 말이오?
That's not it! It's that you just said there is nothing!
그게 아니야! 반찬이 아무것도 없다니!
What's not there is not there!
아무것도 없는 건 없는 거니까!
Musashi, have you ever thought about someone else's feelings?
무사시는 타인의 기분이란 걸 생각해 본 적이 있니?
What?!
뭐라?!
Soreness, sadness, kindness, affliction, sympathy, or compassion!
마음의 쓰라림이라던가, 슬픔이라던가, 친절함이라던가, 앓는 것이라던가, 동정심이라던가, 측은지심이라던가!
I know that!
그 정도는 나도...
Now, now, stop the difficult conversation and just eat.
자, 자, 어려운 이야기는 괜찮으니까 가득 드쇼.
I never had something this good!
이렇게 맛있는 건 난 정말 처음 먹어!
When you're hungry, everything tastes so good.
배가 고프면 뭐든 맛있게 느껴져요.
That's right!
그게 맞소!
Another dish!
한 그릇 더!
Me too!
나도!
Young kids shouldn't be so slim, since chubby ones do taste better!
젊은 것들은 그렇게 해야 말라붙은 놈들보다 통통하게 살쪄있는 게 먹는 맛이 있으니까.
Taste better?
먹는 맛이 있어?
Now, who's next?
자, 다음은 누구냐?
Oh, that's me-dasu!
아, 나이오!
Grandma.
할머니.
What did Musashi just see? Wait for the stormy latter half!
무사시가 본 것은 대체 무엇인가? 질풍노도의 후반을 기다려라!
Tsuchigumo!
츠치구모!
Musashi!
무사시!
What's wrong?
왜 그래?
There's Tsuchigumo!
츠치구모가!
Where is it?!
어디에 있어?!
It just showed a huge shadow over the sliding door!
문 밖에 엄청 큰 그림자를 보였소!
Wasn't it just an illusion out of fear?
또 공포심에 환영을 본 게...
No, I did just feel an eerie malice.
아니, 나도 확실히 방금... 기분 나쁜 살기를 느꼈으니.
It's gonna be tasty when you eat.
먹으면 맛있겠지.
She's griding her knife.
칼을 갈고 있소.
Why?
어째서...
Could it be...
설마...
Check it out, Musashi! Aren't you a samurai?
가봐, 무사시! 사무라이잖아?
You were all talk-dasu!
이런 때만 뺀질거리오!
What's up?
뭔 일이니?
G- grandma, what are you doing-dasu?!
하, 할머니, 뭘 하오!
I was thinking about giving noodles to you people tomorrow morning. The buckwheat around here are plump and good.
내일 아침 모두에게 메밀국수를 주려고 그래서 말야. 이곳 메밀은 살이 번들번들하게 잘 붙어서 맛있어. 자.
So that was it-dasu!
그런 것이었소!
You surprised us!
놀랐잖아, 정말!
My music is probably not what you are looking for.
히카리노스케 씨가 원하는 음악과는 전혀 다르긴 해도.
Nah, it's all right. You're good at it anyway, Osenchan.
으응, 그건 그걸로 괜찮아. 잘하잖아, 오센짱?
Really?
정말?
But I somehow feel that you aren't giving it all your heart.
그래도, 왠지 마음의 집중이 아직 부족한 것 같아.
All my heart?
마음의 집중?
It's true for everything; I think what's most important is the heart, rather than techniques.
뭐든 그렇다 생각하지만, 나, 제일 소중한 것은 기술보다도 마음이라고 생각해.
Heart.
마음.
Especially for musics. I want to bring peace to these turbulent times with my own musics.
음악은 특히 그래. 나, 언젠가는, 이 난세를 내 음악으로 평화한 세상으로 만들어 보이고 싶어.
It might be just a dream, though.
꿈일지도 모르겠지만.
But still, it's an awesome dream.
그래도 멋진 꿈이야.
Just like that, I want to test whether my music will have effect on monsters.
그런 의미로 나, 내 음악이 괴물에게 통할지 아닐지 시험해 보고 싶어.
Have effect?
통한다니?
I mean, I'd like if the monsters stop doing bad things by listening to my music.
그러니까, 괴물이 내 음악을 듣고 나쁜 짓을 하지 않게 되었으면 좋겠는데.
No way that's happening-dasu!
그렇게 될 리가 없소!
Anyhow, our duty might end right here.
어쩌겠냐. 우리 역할은 여기서 끝날지도 모르지.
Huh? Are you saying that Osenchan is going to have that music guy as her husband...?
에? 설마 오센짱이 저 음악놈을 신랑으로 한다는 게...
That's possible.
그럴 가능성도 충분하지.
Impossible! No matter what, Osenchan wouldn't do that with someone who's not a martial artist!
무슨 말을! 뭐가 뭐래도 오센짱이 저런 무예가가 아닌 남자하고...
On the contrary, it's possible that she found him fresh. That's how women are.
그래서야말로 신선하다 느꼈을 수도 있지. 여심이란 그런 것이다.
Huh? You're talking as if you know women well-dasu.
어라? 잘 아는 듯이 그러시오.
Hikarinosuke! Let's...
히카리노스케 씨! 나하고...
Err, no way, you shouldn't decide in hurry-dasu!
아, 설마, 서두르면 안 되오!
Let's play a music together someday!
나하고 언젠가는 같이 연주하자!
-Let's do it together. -Yeah! I can't wait!
-같이 하자. -응! 기대되네!
Me and my expectations-dasu...
진짜, 멋대로 기대했소!
Grandma, the noodles were great!
할머니, 소바 맛있었소!
That's good to hear.
그건 잘 되었구나.
You're guiding us too, and we're grateful for that-dasu!
덕분에 안내도 해줘서 감사하오!
Nah, this is nothing, really.
무슨, 이 정도야 일도 아니지.
I have a bad feeling about this place.
왠지 기분나쁜 곳이야.
You'll see Miyazato village past there.
저기만 넘으면 미야자토 마을이 보일 거야.
This passage is really narrow-dasu.
정말 심하게 좁은 곳이오.
Huh? W- wait!
어라? 자, 잠깐!
Hikarinosuke, wait for me-dasu!
아, 히카리노스케, 기다리시오!
Musashi, hurry up!
무사시, 빨리 가!
I want to, my head's stuck.
아니, 그런 말을 해도 머, 머리가...
Hikarinosuke! What happened-dasu?!
히카리노스케! 무슨 일이오!
Hikarinosuke!
히카리노스케 씨!
Senhime...
센히메...
He was done for with something very sharp.
어지간히 날카로운 것에 당했어.
A string...
실이...
Tsuchigumo's strings.
츠치구모의 실이다.
It's pretty long.
길게 이어져 있어.
Could that grandma be...
그 할머니, 설마...
Musashi! Be careful!
무사시! 조심해라!
Grandma! Where are you-dasu?!
할머니! 어디 있소!
Help me!
살려줘!
The scream of the girl that he saw yesterday. Musashi wouldn't stay put after hearing that.
어제 그 젊은 여자아이의 비명. 그걸 듣고서 가만히 있을 무사시가 아니었다.
That must be...
저건!
That must be Tenchimaru!
저건 틀림없이 천지환!
Help me!
살려줘!
Otama!
오타마!
I'm going right now!
지금 가오!
W-what-
뭐, 뭣이오!
Tsuchigumo!
츠치구모!
It's cowardly to come out of nowhere-dasu!
갑자기 나오다니 비겁하오!
Kojirō!
코지로!
Leave this to me. Musashi, help that girl!
이 녀석은 내게 맡겨라. 무사시는 저 아가씨를!
Come attack me, monster!
와라, 괴물!
Otama, wake up-dasu!
오타마, 정신 차리시오!
Otama, get onto my back-dasu!
오타마, 내 등에 오르시오!
Thank you.
고맙군.
Musashi! She isn't Otama!
무사시! 저건 오타마가 아니야!
Die, Musashi!
죽어라, 무사시!
What are you doing-dasu?!
뭔 짓이오!
Prepare yourself-dasu!
각오하시오!
Are you going to torment an old woman?
이런 늙은이를 괴롭힐 겐가?
Grandma...
할머지...
Musashi!
무사시!
I am Onihime. I'll take Senhime!
나는 오니히메. 센히메를 가져가겠다!
Onihime
오니히메
For what?!
목적이 뭐냐!
A goner-to-be has no use for that information.
죽을 자는 그런 건 몰라도 된다. 무사시와 코지로는 여기가 무덤이라는 걸 아는 걸로 충분하다!
Go, Tsuchigumo!
가라, 츠치구모!
Trying to take Tenchimaru? You'd better die embracing that!
천지환을 빼앗을 셈인가. 그걸 끌어안고 죽어라!
Chink in the armor!
빈틈이다!
Osenchan!
오센짱!
Help me!
살려줘!
-Benkei! -You're in good hands now!
-벤케이! -이제 안심하쇼!
Benkei!
벤케이!
I am Ushiwaka. Let's get rid of them together!
나는 우시와카. 힘을 모아 퇴치를!
Ushiwaka!
우시와카!
Feeling lucky? I'll kill you all!
웃기는군. 다 함께 죽여주지!
Go! Tsuchigumo!
가라! 츠치구모!
Leave the rest to me-dasu!
나머지는 맡겨 주오!
Musashi! Be careful!
무사시! 조심해라!
My Kotetsu!
코테츠가!
This is for Hikarinosuke and Kotetsu-dasu!
히카리노스케와 코테츠의 원수를 갚겠소!
Tenchimaru. It is a wonderful sword-dasu.
천지환. 대단한 검이오.
B- beautiful!
아, 아름다워!
Running away-dasu?!
달아날 셈이오!
We're here to get rid of Onihime and Tsuchigumo after we heard about them.
우리도 오니히메와 츠치구모의 소문을 듣고 퇴치하러 왔습니다.
But still, I didn't expect to meet you here!
그래도 이런 곳에서 만나다니 참!
Can I keep this Tenchimaruto for myself-dasu?
이 천지환, 내가 맡아도 괜찮겠소?
I'm done with collecting swords, so do whatever you want!
칼 모으는 건 관뒀으니까 가져가시라!
Hikarinosuke, you couldn't keep the promise to play the music together.
히카리노스케 씨, 같이 연주하자는 약속, 지키지 못하게 되었네.
Your music will be always in my heart...
당신의 음악은 언제까지나 내 마음 속에...
Musashi's group promised to meet Ushiwaka and Benkei again, and they parted and kept going on their journey.
무사시 일행은 우시와카와 벤케이와 재회를 약속하고 갈라져 다시 여행길을 떠났다.
But there is no way this journey is going to be peaceful and safe. What is waiting for him?
그러나 이 여행이 평온무사할 리가 없다. 다음에 다가올 시련은 무엇인가.
Nonetheless, don't be dispirited, Musashi, Kojirō, and Senhime! Bright future is waiting for you!
어쨌든, 꺾이지 마라, 무사시, 코지로, 센히메! 밝은 희망이 기다리고 있다!
Sometimes the moon jumps over
허공의 주머니에 달이
the pocket of empty sky
뛰어넘어가는 일도 있어
Laugh loudly and
큰 소리로 웃으면
morning will come tomorrow
내일에는 아침이 와
Don't worry too much about losing
잃는 것 따위는 아무것도 아니야
Keep going! Go for it!
계속 해나가! 앞으로 가!
A bare hand is strong
맨손은 강해
That's how it is! Let's go lightly
그런 거야! 가볍게 가자
That's how life is! Look, a chance
인생 그런 거야! 기회가 어라,
follows us wagging its tail!
꼬리를 흔들며 쫒아와!
That's how it is! Let's go lightly
그런 거야! 가볍게 가자
That's how the future is, too! Look, tomorrow
미래도 그런 거야! 내일이 어라,
is opening its hands and smiling at us!
양손을 벌리고 웃고 있어!
I faced Yamata no Orochi that Jūbee told me about-dasu.
주베 씨가 말한 요괴 야마타노오로치를 만났소.
Alright! When I get this thing, I'll have Tenkūmaru in my hands and my technique of dual blades will become machless-dasu!
좋소, 이놈을 잡으면 천공환도 손에 넣고 내 이도류도 천하무적이 되오!
Next Karakuri sorcerer is called Shutentiger.
다음 카라쿠리 요술사의 이름은 슈텐타이가.
Next story! Yamata no Orochi, a Big Showdown!
다음 이야기! 야마타노오로치, 대결전이오!
The techniques of dual blades will be stormy-dasu!
질풍노도의 이도류이오!
Next Episode
다음 이야기
A Big Showdown Against
야마타노오로치, 대결전이오
Yamata no Orochi
기대하세요!